Software Engineer

ZOIS PAGOULATOS

L +31 (0) 6##

zois.dev

zoispag

EXPERIENCE

KYOS Energy Analytics

Web Developer | since April 2017

Software development, software testing, DevOps operations

Freelancer

Web developer | since October 2008

Website design & development

Cosmote

Telecommunications Engineer | May 2015 - March 2017

Broadband network, Voice over Broadband & IPTV support & management

Cosmote

Internship | November 2013 - April 2014

Broadband network support & troubleshooting

EDUCATION

Major in Computer Engineering, University of West Attica, Athens, Greece.

Bachelor of Applied Science (BASc) | 2008 – 2014

SKILLS

Also proficient in UI Testing with tools like Cypress.io and Laravel Dusk, as well as in Unit testing.

- PHP
- JavaScript
- Docker

- Node.js
- Vue
- React

- Laravel
- Tailwind CSS

About me

Experienced Software Engineer with a demonstrated history of working in the computer software industry. Skilled in PHP, Laravel, Unit Testing, Browser Testing (Laravel Dusk), Javascript, Vue.JS and jQuery. Docker enthusiast with feel for automations and CI/CD procedures with TeamCity/Jenkins. Strong